https://www.cyberastro.com/privacy-policy

Multi Concern Report
If you have a single concern related to any area of your life and are looking for a precise answer to your question, you can get it with the help of this report.
Career & Finance
Career Forecast
Education Forecast
Business Venture Forecast
Financial Forecast
Investment Forecast
Get answer to all questions related to your career what, when, how and why a particular incident will take place in professional life. Best report to get career guidance and be prepared in advance.
Love & Marriage
Horoscope Matching
Life Together Analysis
Mars in Marriage
Holistic Love Report
Child Birth Prediction
Explore your chances of marriage with current partner or explore the compatibility issues in married life to let your relationship be on the right track on different astrological parameters based on your horoscope.
Transit & Events
Jupiter Transit Report
Saturn Transit Report
Rahu-Ketu Transit Report
Karma Index Report
Personalised Yearly Prediction
Varshaphal Report
Know the impact of important transit and events on your life with our reports. Explore what changes they bring into your life.
Online Astrology Reports
Vulnerability Index Check
Online Astrology Answer
Online Career Prediction
Online Kundali Matching
Online Manglik Check
Online Saturn Transit
Passion Profile Report
Online Horoscope Prediction
Mind & Body Compatibility
As the name suggests, this section offers an instant online answer, analysis or solution to various issues. Explore
astrology reports in this section. Get online astrology answer to any question, online horoscope matching, career report and a lot more to explore.
Horoscope
Daily Horoscope
Daily horoscope readings or predictions are based on the astrology signs and the planetary movements that bring changes in different aspects of your life focusing on the prime in the daily basis.
Check Your Daily Horoscope...
Weekly Horoscope
Weekly Horoscope predictions based on your Zodiac Sun Sign & know what lies ahead in your upcoming week in different aspects like career, finance, heath & Your love life.
Check Your Weekly Horoscope...
Monthly Horoscope
Get Monthly horoscope predictions for all 12 zodiac signs. Cyberastro forecasts the predictions based on Vedic astrology on a monthly basis with your birth chart.
Check Your Monthly Horoscope...
Yearly Horoscope
Get most accurate astrological predictions and yearly horoscope for all 12 zodiac signs with the yearly predictions for the upcoming year and plan your life ahead in the most productive manner.
Check Your Yearly horoscope...
Free Horoscope Chart
Janam Kundali, Janam Patri Online/Natal Chart determines one’s future astrology predictions by date of birth and it's one of the most significant aspects of Vedic astrology predictions.
Check Your Horoscope Chart...
Gemstones
Natural Ruby
Natural Ruby Gemstones or Manik is recommended by astrologers to be worn for getting ultimate success and growth in businesses, jobs, social status and self-confidence and also people with a deficient Sun in their birth chart.
Natural Pearl
Natural Pearl is highly rare and considered extremely auspicious in the world of Vedic astrology. It increases your mental stability and strengthens the power of planet Moon.
Natural Red Coral
The Natural Red Coral gemstones are advised to be worn by Vedic astrologers to boost the energy of Mars in an individual’s horoscope and provide them stability and success in different fronts of life.
Natural Emerald
Natural emerald helps an individual to benefit in all the important aspects of life and has a high influence of planet Mercury. Let this precious Natural emerald gemstone enlighten your life with positivity.
Natural Yellow Sapphire
The Natural Yellow Sapphire gemstone represents Planet Jupiter and is worn for achieving professional success, marital bliss and improved mental and physical being.
Natural White Sapphire
Natural White sapphire is the alternative for diamonds representing the planet of Beauty and wisdom, Venus. This gemstone can help in improving our artistic skills, beauty, passion and affection in personal life.
Natural Blue Sapphire
Wearing a Natural Blue Sapphire Gemstone promotes the attitude of being careful, strong, profound and confident. The gemstone represents planet Saturn and is the ultimate source of positivity.
Natural Hessonite
A Natural Hessonite Gemstone also known as Gomed is ruled by Rahu planet in our birth chart can put magical effects in the life of its wearer by impacting the Karma Indicators controlled by Rahu.
Natural Cat's Eye
According to the Vedic astrology, natural Cat’s Eye gemstone represents the Planet - Ketu, which symbolizes our past karma and wearing it can actually give your wisdom and a great intellect.
Remedies
Energized Yantra
Planetary Yantras
Hanuman Kavach
Balarishta Yantra
Shree Yantra Pendant
Shree Yantra
Planetary Yantras helps you to neutralize malefic planets and brings positive energies. The planetary Yantra will cure the ill effects of the nine planets in your Birth Chart .It will bless you with happiness, prosperity and fortune.
Vedic Astrology Yagna
Shani Shanti Yagna
Manglik Shanti Yagna
Kaal Sarpa Shanti Yagna
Mangla Gauri Yagna
Personal Rudrabhishek
Katyaani Yagna
Personal Ganpati Yagna
Mahamrityunjay Yagna
Santan Gopal Yagna
Personal Kanakdhara Yagna
Shanti Shanti Yagna is performed to get rid of problems like poverty, tension, insult, displeasure for you and your family members when going through the Sade Sati period.
Vedic Ceremonies
Hanuman Jayanti Ceremony
Kanak Dhara Yagna
Deepawali Celebration
Rudram Chamakam Yagna
Hanuman Jayanti Ceremony on the auspicious eve of the birthday of Lord Hanuman is done to ensure his blessings and positivity to fulfill all the desires of the devotee.
Astrology
Vedic Astrology
Vedic astrology online for free for each zodiac sign, free Vedic astrology prediction 2020 as Birth chart, know what lies in your future as per Vedic astrology or Hindu astrology, explore Vedic horoscope for 2020, free of cost based on your ascendant, Moon and Sun sign
Child Astrology
Child Astrology helps you understand your children as they grow up and evolve in life. Cyber Astro’s paid and free Child Astrology Reports provides information on child’s future, baby astrology compatibility with parent and other aspects.
Numerology
Know more about Numerology Prediction 2020 and get free numerology reports at Cyber Astro. Get to know the numerology compatibility, Numerology calculator, numerology compatibility, name numerology number, Destiny Number, Nature Number for free.
Vastu Services
Residential Vastu
Commercial Vastu
Free Vastu Tips
Newly built or already living in your home, flat or bunglow. Ensure prosperity, happiness and progress by taking the right guidance from our vastu experts. Fill your home with tremendous luck!
Free Services
Monthly Vedic Sky
Vedic Sky
Find out what changes does planets make while they transit into different signs. Get to know what things they reveal. Follow the general predictions with our Monthly Vedic Sky section. Avail the free service.
Vedic Remedies
Vedic Remedies
Having some troubles in different sectors like education, health, career, finance and love-life?
Take the free general services and know about the best suited remedy for you.
Heal yourself with the best remedies provided by us.
Vedic Muhuratam
Muhuratam for Naamkaran
Muhuratam for Marriage
Muhuratam to Start Medicine
Muhuratam to Start Business
Muhuratam to Start Job
Muhuratam to Start Education
Muhuratam for Travel
Muhuratam for Home Entrance
Property & Vehicle Purchase
Muhuratam for Annaprashan
Know the perfect time when to perform the naming ceremony of your new born. Conducting naming ceremony in the auspicious time bring fortune and luck to your loved child to attain a delightful and joyous life. Get the shubh muhuratam for Naamkaran to your child.
Free Astrology Reports
Yearly Prediction
Career & Finance
Love & Relationship
Whole Life Predictions
Transit of Planets
Free Birth Chart
Check out the free annual predictions for you, covering various aspects of your life. Get it done by just knowing the date, time and place of your birth. Know what the upcoming year beholds for you…
Astrology Articles / Blogs
Astrology Articles
Astrology Blogs
Reading always gives us a pleasure. Continue with this activity by reading the well researched articles by our well-known astrologers and team.
0
Login
Signup
Personalised Yearly Prediction 2021
Life is full of changes and challenges. With each passing year, it increases the potential and your chances to get through the ups and downs that come in life on your own. BOOK NOW
Jupiter Transit Report
Jupiter transit is one of the major planetary transit of the year. This transit is considered as one of the most auspicious planetary transit and has extreme importance in the world of Vedic astrology.
BOOK NOW
Vulnerability Index Check
In this unprecedented time for the world, having strong immune system is primary weapon to fight and defeat the Virus COVID-19.
Know More
Rahu Ketu Transit Report
Know all about the effect on your personal, professional and financial life that Planet Rahu and Ketu will bring in your life when they transit into Taurus and Scorpio respectively.
BOOK NOW
Multi Concern Report
If you are having multiple concerns at a time related to diffrent aspcets of life and wants address all at once then this is the best report to get answer and find solution to all in a signle report.
Book Now
Live Astro Counselling
Want to get instant solutions to your concerns and questions related to different aspects of your life? Talk or connect directly to online expert astrologer one to one and find a solution
Know More
Home
/ Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
At Cyber Astro, Ltd.
We take the privacy of the information you provide us very seriously. This statement demonstrates our firm commitment to our privacy policy. Please read this carefully to understand how we use any information you provide us at www.cyberastro.com.
Cyber Astro Ltd. guarantees complete confidentiality of our member's identity, horoscope details and the prediction details.
Cyber Astro Ltd. further guarantees that no direct or indirect use will be made by Cyber Astro about any aspect of life, as revealed in the horoscope of a member, except for the explicit purpose of communicating the horoscope charts and predictions back to the member.
We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
We allow members to access their user profiles and change information, as they deem necessary.
Since new items will get added to our services as we modify and expand, we would suggest you to check the website on a regular basis in order to understand how we treat your information. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what personal information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Your continued use of the site will constitute your acknowledgment of our Privacy Policy.
This document is rather long because we want to give our users all the facts about our privacy policy. The items below provide an index to the information that follows.
What personal information do we collect?
Registration Data
During membership registration, Cyber Astro collects personal information including your name, gender, email address, your current hometown and birth data information including your time of birth. This information is used strictly to generate your personal horoscopes online. Your email address is used to identify your unique birth data record in the database, since an email address is always unique and has no duplicates. You do not have to provide any personal information to use Cyber Astro services. However, if you choose not to become a member of Club Cyber Astro, we may not be able to provide you with some of the other services dependent upon the collection of such information, such as your personalized free predictions.
Through Log Files
Our server and statistics server capture information to gather broad demographic information that is not personal. We track the IP address of visitors to the site to find out demographically which parts of the world our traffic comes from. We collect browser types used and access times to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movements within the site to find out what services are most appealing. All of this information is used for gathering broad demographic data to enhance the performance and services of the site.
Through Order Forms
For our paid personalized services, we basically gather the information needed for fulfillment of the service. This is held in strict confidence, as explained earlier. We guarantee complete confidentiality of our member's identity, horoscope details and the prediction details. Cyber Astro Ltd. further guarantees that no direct or indirect use will be made by Cyber Astro about any aspect of life, as revealed in the horoscope of a member, except for the explicit purpose of communicating the horoscope charts and predictions back to the member.
For payment of the paid services, we use two independent secure server companies, Bank Card USA for International Cards and Pay seal of ICICI Bank Ltd. for Indian Credit cards. Your credit card information, as well as your address for address verification is collected by this company on their website and Cyber Astro Ltd. has no access to this information.
Other information that we may collect
Any other information we may have for you, comes from actual email or other contact you may have made with us in regard to specific services or products. As a general rule, these are not made part of your member profile, and are used only to address your specific need or concern that you may have communicated to us on. Although we give you the option to tell your friends about our site, we do not monitor or keep any record of friends you may contact. Information gathered on our “Affiliate with Us”, is used primarily for a Business-to-Business purpose and to encourage inquiries from other web sites that might be interested in obtaining our Astrology content for their own site. Information from “Advertise with Us” similarly is used to generate interest in other sites or companies that may wish to purchase banner advertising on our site.
PREDICTION
Live Astro Counselling
Jupiter Transit Report
Health Report
Yearly Prediction
Saturn Transit Forecast
Life Prediction Report
HOROSCOPE
Terms of Use | Refunds & Cancellation Policy | Disclaimer | Privacy policy | About Us | Site Map  |  Advertise  |  Career With Us | Contact Us
Copyright 2020 @ Cyber Astro Limited
Notifications
×
See All
